<resources>
    <string-array name="advice_titles">
        <item>Writing passwords down</item>
        <item>Do not reuse passwords</item>
        <item>Do not trust in L33t</item>
        <item>What not to use</item>
        <item>Password managers</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="advice_contents">
        <item>If you need to write down your passwords, it is OK,
            as long as you keep it stored in your wallet,
            along with the rest of your personal items. \n\n
            Just do not write it in a post it on your monitor! </item>
        <item>Never use one password for several services! \n\n
            If a hacker is able to steal your password in one site, then all
            your sites are compromised. \n\n
            In fact, an easy way for a hacker to steal passwords, is to set up
            a service that requires a subcription with login and password,
            and then use that password in the other sites of the victims.
        </item>
        <item> Sometimes the L33t (leet) alphabet is used to transform a simple word in a password
            by substituting some of its letters with numbers or symbols, like in "Pa$$w0rd". \n\n
            This is a bad idea! The tools used by hackers are aware of this technique and can
            easily apply these permutations to dictionaries to break these passwords.
        </item>
        <item>Do not use any recognizable word or data as a password. This includes: any word in a dictionary;
            movie titles; names of places, characters or pets; memorable but public dates as the birthday of
            your father or the date of your wedding; any of the previous ones accompanied by a number.
        </item>
        <item>If you have several different passwords to handle at the same time, you may consider using
            a password manager. \n\n
            A password manager is a software where you can safely store passwords in an encrypted file,
            that only you can access using a master password. But remember to be extra careful with this
            oner, as if it is compromised, then all your other passwords will be too!
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="technique_titles">
        <item>With a sentence</item>
        <item>Passphrase</item>
        <item>From word or root</item>
        <item>Mnemonics</item>
        <item>PsychoPass</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="technique_contents">
        <item>Pick a sentence, and form a password with the first
letter and the number of letters of each word.
For greater security, add symbols (length 0), and uppercase. \n\n
For example, from the phrase: "Con cien cañones por banda!" \n\n
we obtain the password: C3c4c6p3b5!</item>
        <item>If your password policy allows it,
simply pick a long sentence with at least 3 or four words. \n\n
For greater strength, with numbers, uppercase and symbols. \n\n
For example: MargaretThatcherIs100%Sexy
        </item>
        <item>Choose a more or less long word, and break it in two parts,
separated with one or several symbols.\n\n
For example: from the word "revolution", we can get the password: rev%%olution.\n\n
For stronger passwords you can use several words: Sil%%ent--rev%%olution
        </item>
        <item>Choose a random, strong password, then invent a mnemonic to memorize it. \n\n
Choose a word for every letter forming a sentence. Incorprorate the numbers and symbols in the
phrase so that they have some meaning. The sentence does not need to make much sense,
just by choosing the set of words the memorization will be easy.\n\n
For example, from the password: Ch_t3cq7AM, we could make up the sentence:\n\n
"Charles had underlined the three careful quilts at 7 a.m."\n\n
This method is specially useful for the case where the system chooses the password for you.
        </item>
        <item> This method is based in the disposition of the keys in a keyboard. Choose an initial
key, and a sequence of movements taking us from one letter to the next.\n\n
For example, if we take the letter "h" and the sequence: "Up, right, up, left" the resulting
password would be: hyu76. \n\n
With this technique, we can generate many different passwords by memorizing a single sequence,
and then choosing different keys as starting points.\n\n
Also, to make stronger passwords, you can choose two keys instead of one, and execute the
sequence twice. With the previous sequence, using "h" and also the character ".", the password
would be: hyu76.lkio
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="activateTipTitle">Activate Personal Attack Dictionary</string>
    <string name="activateTipContent">Now that you are capable of creating strong password,
try a more strict analysis that mimics what a hacker would do. \n\n
Obtain more information and activate this option selecting the \"Personal Dictionary\" menu item.
    </string>

</resources>
